{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","address":"20143 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221","owner":"Tameka Watkins","licenseNumber":"202881","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"6/6/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000A059D73D19C954C030EE820593384540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43563","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","inspectionDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"83","pcount":"0","pfcount":"5","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"5","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"8/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make easily accessible."},{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"8/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"8/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"8/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"8-303.10","violationDescription":"For FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS that are required to submit plans as specified under ยง 8-201.11 the REGULATORY AUTHORITY shall issue a PERMIT to the applicant after:\r\n(A) A properly completed application is submitted;\r\n(B) The required fee is submitted;\r\n(C) The required plans, specifications, and information are reviewed and APPROVED; and\r\n(D) A preoperational inspection as specified in ยง 8-203.10 shows that the establishment is built or remodeled in accordance with the APPROVED plans and specifications and that the establishment is in compliance with this Code.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"8/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"8/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"8/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"A designated dressing room/area shall be provided and used."},{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"8/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."},{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"8/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]},{"inspectionid":"40960","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","inspectionDate":"2017-12-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40960","inspectionDate":"12/1/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make easily accessible."},{"inspectionid":"40960","inspectionDate":"12/1/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"38626","establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","inspectionDate":"2017-05-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2110"}}